Filardo, Anne Documents regarding Teachers Action Caucus (TAC-UFT) 5795
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Anne Filardo Documents regarding Teachers Action Caucus (TAC-UFT)
1968-1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Filardo, Anne
5795
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5706184
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 30, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Teachers' unions--New York (State); Filardo, Anne L.; Teachers Action Caucus.; United Federation of Teachers.
5706184
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Pamphlets, brochures
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Newsletters, Pamphlets, Brochures
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- United Federation of Teachers, Statements on Community Control, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Newsletters, Pamphlets, Speeches
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Pamphlets, Newsletters
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Minutes, Mailers, Pamphlets
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Minutes, Flyers, Newsletters
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Brochures, Minutes, Newsletters
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Brochures, Mailers, Minutes, Articles
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Articles, Minutes, Newsletters
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Newsletters, Pamphlets, Articles, Minutes
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Newsletters, Minutes, Pamphlets
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Mailers, Minutes, Articles
- Teachers Action Caucus, Misc. Materials, 1968-1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Articles, Mailers
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Mailers, Articles, Minutes
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Minutes, Reports, Mailers
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Minutes, Mailers, Articles
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Minutes, Newsletters, Notes
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Minutes, Newsletters, Correspondence
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Minutes, Mailers, Notes
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Minutes, Mailers, Correspondence
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Correspondence, Minutes, Mailers
- Documents RE: American Federation of Teachers Convention, Boston, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  July
- Documents RE: American Federation of Teachers Convention, Boston, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- American Teacher Federation Los Angeles Conventions, Misc. Materials, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles Conference Misc. Materials, continued, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Minutes, Mailers, Documents
- American Federation of Teachers Convention, New York City, Misc. Materials, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Newsletters, Mailers, Minutes
- American Federation of Teachers Convention, Denver, Materials, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- American Federation of Teachers, QUEST Conference, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Articles, Minutes
- American Federation of Teachers QUEST Conference, Materials, continued, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Articles, Minutes, Plans
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Teaches Action Caucus, Materials, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Minutes, Articles, Mailers
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- American Federation of Teachers Convention, Chicago, Materials, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- American Federation of Teachers Convention, San Francisco, Materials, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- American Federation of Teachers QUEST Conference, Materials, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- American Federation of Teachers Convention, D.C., Materials, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  August
- American Federation of Teachers QUEST Conference, Materials, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Teachers Action Caucus, Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Articles, Minutes, Mailers